mosis.com 2019-12-15

# MOSIS Web Site Privacy Statement

### Information We Collect 

The information collected by MOSIS of our customers is initiated by the Customer for information or that required to process orders. 

### Personal Information

MOSIS does not collect or maintain any information about MOSIS users beyond that required to conduct our business. We record basic personal information that may include: your name, email address, IP address, company name, job title, country, work address, phone, choice of technology, order information, design fabrication information, U.S. export compliance information, and all information provided to us by you via our regular website forms. Most of this essential information refers to the commercial concerns, governmental organizations, and educational institutions that hold accounts with MOSIS, and not to individuals. 

We request e-mail addresses in order to facilitate communications with designers and account liaisons. Interested persons may voluntarily give us their e-mail address so that they can receive the occasional announcements that MOSIS distributes to our user community. Account contact and newsletter e-mail address lists are never disclosed outside MOSIS or made available to any other organization or institution. 

Participants in the MOSIS Educational Program (MEP) may be asked, as a condition of participation, to permit disclosure by MOSIS of some general information about their submitted and fabricated designs to the foundry in which they fabricate their designs. 

Statistical analysis of demographics, account type, and fabrication technologies is required to keep MOSIS’ business focused on customer needs. We therefore collect, use, and share statistical and demographic data which is specific to the type of user, their location, and the fabrication technologies which they use. No personal data is included in analysis data. 

### Cookies

Cookies which are used to enhance the functionality and usability of our web presence. Cookies can be used to store items of data on your computer when you access our website. You have the option of preventing the storage of cookies on your computer by making appropriate changes to your browser settings. However, if you do so, you may reduce the range of functionalities offered by our website. 

### External Links

MOSIS provides links to other web sites that we think may be useful to VLSI designers. MOSIS is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of any of these linked sites. 

### Data Protection Rights

To exercise any of the following data protection rights you can submit a Request to the MOSIS Support Center: 

  * When you are asked to provide Personal Data, you may decline, but in certain such cases, MOSIS may not be able to provide its technology or service.
  * Request the correction of your Personal Data when incorrect, out of date or incomplete.
  * We provide our users with an option to unsubscribe from our distribution lists in every mass email sent using Personal Data. 
  * Request that we stop using your Personal Data for direct marketing (either through specific channels or all channels). 
  * Request that we stop any consent-based processing of your Personal Data;
  * Object to our processing of your Personal Data where that processing is based upon Legitimate Interest and there are no compelling grounds for the continued processing of that data.
  * Request that Personal Data be erased.
  * However, please note that we may continue to retain, or otherwise use your Personal Data thereafter where we have a Legitimate Interest or a legal or contractual obligation to do so.
  * Contact your local data protection authority with regard to any data protection questions or concerns.

### Web Server Logs

We maintain standard web server transaction logs, which include the IP address and time of day, and the specific web page associated with requests received by our web server. We use this information only to monitor the way visitors navigate our pages, so that we might improve the organization of the site, and for the purpose of detecting and correcting server problems, including malicious intrusions and attacks.

### Updates

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. Please look for our the most updated Privacy Policy at our website.

### Comments and Questions

Please direct any comments or questions regarding the MOSIS Web Site Privacy Policy to the MOSIS Support Center.   
You can read more information about USC’s Privacy Policy [here](https://policy.usc.edu/).
